Within the Clover's fifth leaf, there lives a devil.
Asta, born unable to harness mana,
was granted the power of anti-magic from his five-leaf grimoire,
giving him the ability to nullify spells.
Unfortunately, the members of Spade Kingdom's Dark Triad
also possessed powers from the devils of the underworld
and used them to launch an invasion on the neighboring countries.
Gaining strength from his belief in himself
and from the support of his friends,
Asta continues to fight for the safety of this world.
Are you ready, Undine?
Of course.
The Heart Kingdom was attacked by the Dark Disciples
who wielded the power of devils.
Leading this attack was Vanica, one of the Dark Triad,
who was possessed by the devil called Magicula.
Meanwhile, after relocating to the neutral zone
between the Clover and Spade Kingdoms,
the Black Bulls were confronted by Dante,
another member of this evil trio.
Spade's attacking us here?
Go, Rouge!
Vanessa's spell and Asta's anti-magic
helped them defend the hideout momentarily,
but Dante's power was too great.
Have it your way.
Perhaps you'll be more driven
if I appeal to your feelings.
Don't do it!
Oh, no!
Gosh!
Gosh was dealt a mortal blow.
Asta's rage and hatred caused him to go berserk.
And finally, he landed a hit.
It seems you've left a small scratch.
You'll regret that.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
You'll regret it.
You will regret it.
Oh, no!
Gosh!
Gosh was dealt a mortal blow.
And finally, he landed a hit.
It seems you've left a small scratch.
Oh, no!
Gosh!
Gosh was dealt a mortal blow.
Asta's rage and hatred caused him to go berserk.
You'll regret that.
I hate to sully my hands in worldly fights.
But now, gravity magic.
Heavy in fighting.
I've got an insatiable urge to beat you to a pulp with my own two fists.
Gosh, please don't die.
You have to live.
Please.
Get it on. Get it on.
始めよう.
難航不落のリアリティ.
立ち止まる時間は無いさ.
Hold on. Hold on.
Yeah!
Let it start.
Fight for liberty.
真実性.
飲み込む常識.
Overway.
逆境の先にある朝.
Oh yeah!
幻想に埋もれた人生の夢.
Hands up!
Shout it! Shout it! Louder!
Yes! Do it! Do it! Start it!
Never give up!
限界を超えてもかすくして experience.
We can't pay! Let's go!
Believe in myself!
衝動的に突き進め! Don't be afraid!
誰よりも高く飛べ! Take it to the sky!
想像を超えた世界をこの手に!
The ground up!
想像せよいつ悪いどない自然の道!
Yes! It's a ground up!
キ DIRECT!
Hey! Yeah!
Believe in myself!
Believe in yourself!
Hey! Yeah! Yeah!
The ground up!
How dare you show yourself like that in front of me!
You ugly thing!
Honestly, my daughters are so beautiful,
but you have to be such a plain and gloomy little wretch!
You made Mother mad again!
Get back to cleaning and take care of the laundry and dishes too while you're at it!
I'm trying!
You're covered in soot! How disgusting!
Then again, your name is Gray, so it's only right for you to be dusty!
Yes, it really suits her!
You should get even dustier to cover up how embarrassingly ugly you are!
That's true! It'll be better if you walk around covered in soot all the time!
Mother, look at this!
My goodness, that spell is so beautiful! Just like the two of you!
Next, dear! I can do that too!
I'm sorry! I didn't mean to!
What are you doing spying on us, you ugly girl?
She's probably jealous of the beautiful magic that we can do!
She's so hideous! She can only dream of pulling that off!
A laggard like you isn't capable of magic that's useful, let alone beautiful!
Step to your chores! Am I clear?
Um, yes!
I have nothing, and I always get yelled at for being a failure!
But if I work as hard as I can, maybe my stepmother and stepsisters will change their minds!
So, you've been sneaking around and shirking your chores in favor of practicing magic!
Have you at least learned any decent spells?
It's been five years since you got your grimoire, hasn't it?
Even a dullard like you must have mastered something by now!
Go ahead, show us a spell!
I'm sure it'll be sad and embarrassing, just like you are, but give it your best!
Now I can be like you two!
How dare you try to imitate us!
We're the ones who are giving these gorgeous faces by mother!
You have no right to look this way!
Change yourself back right this instant!
I'm sorry, I haven't learned how to change back yet!
You're a wolf of an idiot!
We'll kill you!
I finally learned the spell that my magic wasn't enough to fix things!
If I go back home, who knows what they'll do to me!
Then again, am I really capable of living out here on my own?
Well, it's one of you pretty young things from the Whiteleaf family!
You all alone out here?
We're just a trio of starving bandits!
Can you spare something to help us?
I'm sorry, I don't have any money, so I'm afraid there isn't anything I can do for you!
Well, your family has plenty!
Maybe we can just take you!
I'm helpless!
Come on, let's grab her!
Oh, no!
Nice lady!
Are you hurt?
I'm fine!
Thank you so much!
Don't get the wrong idea!
The only reason I bothered to save you was because Marie wanted me to!
Isn't she sweet?
Good girl!
You really are an angel!
You know that Marie?
My precious, adorable little angel!
Thank you for helping her, big brother!
Of course!
Anything for you, Marie!
I didn't know siblings could be that close!
That's nice!
I wish I had...
Hey!
What are you doing out here alone?
Well, the truth is...
You should probably go back home now.
You ran away?
If you did it because of something stupid, you might as well turn around.
Trust me, you'll never survive in this rotten excuse for a world if you don't have the resolve to fight tooth and nail for the life you want.
Gosh probably didn't realize it.
Up until then, I'd had nothing.
But that was what I needed.
Not long after that...
You know what?
I like you.
Come and join my squad.
What are you standing around for, newbie?
You should come have a drink with me.
Hey, Gosh!
Think you could be a little more sociable?
No, leave me alone.
I'm far too busy burning the image of my precious Marie into my retinas.
Ugh, come on now.
Is your sister really the only thing that interests you?
Of course she is!
She's perfect!
Yeah, yeah.
She's an angel!
Gushu...
I was able to see you again.
Maybe I'm going overboard by calling it fate.
But you were the one who led me to the Black Bulls.
The place I belong.
I don't want to lose a single one of my dear friends!
You gave me a reason to keep living, and...
No matter what you look like, you're still Grey.
Because of you, I found friends that I could trust, like family.
I want to save you, and...
It's embarrassing, but I want you to look at me more!
And see how strong I've become!
Grey.
She sealed the wound.
I didn't know her transformation magic could do that.
What is this spell?
Hey, Grey.
How'd you...
Asta!
Magnificent!
Yet another arcane stage fighter!
Your abilities are going to waste in this place.
It's been decided.
You'll both be my women now.
That's my squad.
So keep your mitts off of them.
Captain!
Well then.
You must be Yamisuke Hiro.
And you must be a devil possessed from spade.
But I don't give a damn.
Because whoever you are, I'm about to slaughter you.
I like your malice.
That said, you're out of line.
Gravity magic.
Presence of the Demon King.
I can't control my portal.
Oh?
So you refuse to genuflect.
How bold of you.
I've learned a lot in the last six months.
Time to try it out.
Monosone.
And black hole.
Dark magic.
Black moon.
Interesting.
Any of my magic within that field is being erased.
So this is dark magic.
That's fine.
I'll send this boulder flying at top speed and crush you with the inertia.
Dark magic.
Dark close.
Dimension slash.
He cut through space.
Impressive.
Precisely why I've been searching for you.
Gravity magic.
Heavy infighting gladiator.
He's fast.
I'm using Monosone and predicting his moves by reading his key.
He's not on Julius's level.
But he can control the speed of his sword using gravity.
I was right about you, Yamisuke hero.
Have you been stalking me or something, you weirdo?
Because you're starting to creep me out to something fierce.
Stalking?
Well, you're the one I'm after, so I suppose so.
Look, pal.
It's going to be hard for me to take that as a compliment when it's coming from the likes of you.
You are a key that connects this world to the underworld.
Underworld?
Take that creepy crap and shove it where the sun don't shine!
My, what a shame.
I wasn't expecting Yamisuke hero to be so vulgar and shabby in person.
Say that again!
How did a slob like you manage to recruit so many talented warriors?
I've never been jealous of a human before.
Thank you for inspiring this new malice.
In any case, those Arcane Stage ladies are coming with me.
They're going to serve my ends from now on, not yours.
Captain Mommy!
If they're Arcane Stage, then that's the first I've heard about it.
And they're not here to serve me.
I just brought them on because I liked them.
Monizome, condense.
Dark Cloak to E-Eye Slash.
They're not going anywhere.
Not with you, you damn freak.
The enemy's attacking!
Run!
The queens want us to stop the fire!
Over here!
Hurry!
What?
This can't be.
I knew they had the Devil's power.
They're stronger than I expected.
I'll go do what I can.
Kaza!
If the Spirit Guardians don't stand a chance, then everyone else is doomed.
We have to stop Luck and the others who just left to provide backup.
Laura Pechka!
Don't worry, I'm sure they'll be fine.
You should concentrate on protecting your kingdom.
The queen is absolutely essential.
Not just for protecting Heart, but for attacking Spade as well.
We'll protect you no matter what it takes.
I don't care how strong they are.
I won't let us be beaten.
No way.
That was one of the Heart Kingdom's elite spirit guardians.
How disappointing.
But not surprising, I guess.
Of course I'm more powerful.
I'm Lady Banaka's right-hand man.
With 50% of the Devil's power.
One of the Dark Disciples.
None other than the great Svenken Gizzard.
Looks like I've still got some clean-up to do.
No!
Huh?
What's this?
Well, what do you know?
A cute little kid's come out to play with me.
Hmm?
You're not from this kingdom, are you?
You should probably run on back to where you belong.
Heck no!
I like your speed, but it's not enough.
Goodbye, kiddo!
Lightning magic!
Thunderbolt destruction!
Nice try, but with my magic, I can change the shape and hardness of my skin.
I transform it as needed to nullify the effects of my opponent's spells.
With its various capabilities, my body's the ultimate spear and shield.
No matter what you try.
You stand no charge in this fight!
I'm way into the zero stage.
In your first stage at the most.
Fast or not, there's no way you're going to beat me.
You should use that speed of yours to run away.
Why would I want to run away?
This is way too much fun!
Oh, I get it now.
You're young and stupid.
What are you doing here?
Why attack the Heart Kingdom?
I would do anything, my Lady Vanica asked of me.
No woman can beat her when it comes to power and beauty.
She's an idol.
Someone to be worshipped and obeyed.
Ah.
So you'll go around hurting people because she wants you to?
That's reason enough for me.
And you?
Why put your life on the line for strangers,
people who aren't even from your country?
Just look how beat up and bloody you are, little guy.
You're pretty selfish, stealing others' happiness to impress someone.
You go ahead and do what you gotta do, look!
But so will I, got it?
I'll do what I've gotta do.
And protect them.
I'll do it.
Because I'm a magic knight!
Hey, Gaja, can you show me how to do the true lightning magic that you use?
As the name suggests, it is a spell that produces a real lightning bolt.
I am a spirit guardian, and it still took me two years to learn it.
Aw, too bad.
It seemed like a whole lot of fun.
As an expert at discharge spells, I'm well-suited to that kind of technique.
I would say that your streak lies with equip spells, however.
You have the ability to instantly form a raise near your hands and your feet.
Use that to your advantage, and create your own uniquely powerful spell.
I don't care how fast or determined you are, it won't help you now.
Your magic is useless against me, and you're in bad shape, so why not give up?
Seriously!
Oh, come on!
It's never gonna work, kid.
My skin can detect your mana, you know.
It reacts automatically to protect me from harm!
He's just a piece of his armor, huh?
A clever thing to do, I'll give you that much.
In exchange, I'll show you how clever I can be!
Skin magic! Skin fort!
Magic shell for all!
Faster! Faster!
You're a tough one, aren't you?
Your mana won't hold out much longer, though.
Don't worry, when you exhaust yourself, I'll give you the treatment you deserve.
More! Faster!
What? How did he inflict that much damage?
Is he moving faster than my skin's ability to sense mana?
In that case, I'm just going to make my defense even harder to get through.
Let's see how badly you can hurt me now that I'm as solid as a rock wall.
Huh?
More!
Wait, hold on.
Something isn't right about this.
Just what are you up to, brat?
More!
My skin magic will stand up against anything you can throw at me!
Faster!
Whatever you're doing won't work!
True lightning magic!
Kitter-mouse!
He went through me?
But there's no way.
Did he use that spell to turn himself into a bolt of actual lightning?
That was fun.
Thanks for the fight.
Shut up.
Hey, don't forget to catch up with us.
Let's see.
connections
Come on
Here we are!
There's no way.
There is no wayessionals in the fight.
So long tiempo
separating me
I'm not sure how to fly
Beautiful
What's your view?
I'm not sure how to fly
The world is so beautiful
Hey
Today's the day
Look, isn't she the cutest?
So cute it hurts
Today's the day
Cute, right?
They seem to be doing that a lot lately
I wonder what it's about
Nice communication, guys
That was awesome!
I wonder what everyone else is up to
If they don't hurry
I'll beat everyone here myself
Black Clover
Page 164
Battlefield
Heart Kingdom
Fighting a strong enemy is the best